{
  "questionList":{
    "question1":[
      {
        "id":1,
        "question":"Who founded Apple Computer?",
        "option1":"Stephen Fry",
        "option2":"Bill Gates",
        "option3":"Steve Jobs",
        "answer":"Steve Jobs"
      },
      {
        "id":2,
        "question":"Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
        "option1":"Motherboard",
        "option2":"Keyboard",
        "option3":"Mouse",
        "answer":"Motherboard"
      },
      {
        "id":3,
        "question":"What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
        "option1":"Wide Width Wickets",
        "option2":"Worldwide Weather",
        "option3":"World Wide Web",
        "answer":"World Wide Web"
      },
      {
        "id":4,
        "question":"When did the compact disc first appear on the market?",
        "option1":"1982",
        "option2":"1983",
        "option3":"1985",
        "answer":"1982"
      },
      {
        "id":5,
        "question":"Which of these is a file format for digital images?",
        "option1":"CIA",
        "option2":"JPG",
        "option3":"IBM",
        "answer":"JPG"
      },
      {
        "id":6,
        "question":"What is SMTP stands for?",
        "option1":"Simple Mail Transfer Protocol",
        "option2":"Simple Messege Transfer Protocol",
        "option3":"Sample Mail Transfer Protocol",
        "answer":"Simple Mail Transfer Protocol"
      },
      {
        "id":7,
        "question":"What is VPN stands for?",
        "option1":"Virtual Personal Network",
        "option2":"Virtual Private Network",
        "option3":"Visual Private Network",
        "answer":"Virtual Private Network"
      },
      {
        "id":8,
        "question":".xls is a file extension used in which application?",
        "option1":"Ms Excel",
        "option2":"Ms Office",
        "option3":"Ms Powerpoint",
        "answer":"Ms Excel"
      },
      {
        "id":9,
        "question":"Which is not a web browser?",
        "option1":"Chrome",
        "option2":"Safari",
        "option3":"Gmail",
        "answer":"Gmail"
      },
      {
        "id":10,
        "question":"What is the full form of UPS?",
        "option1":"Uninterruptible Power Supply.",
        "option2":"Uninterruptible Program Supply.",
        "option3":"Uniform Power Supply.",
        "answer":"Uninterruptible Power Supply."
      },
      {
        "id":11,
        "question":"Which is not an Internet protocol?",
        "option1":"IP",
        "option2":"STP",
        "option3":"HTTP",
        "answer":"STP"
      },
      {
        "id":12,
        "question":"Another name for a computer chip is?",
        "option1":"Micro chip",
        "option2":"Execute",
        "option3":"Microprocessor",
        "answer":"Micro chip"
      },
      {
        "id":13,
        "question":"In what year was the @ chosen for its use in e-mail addresses?",
        "option1":"1976",
        "option2":"1972",
        "option3":"1974",
        "answer":"1972"
      },
      {
        "id":14,
        "question":"What is the full form of CD?",
        "option1":"Copy Density",
        "option2":"Change Data",
        "option3":"Compact Disc",
        "answer":"Compact Disc"
      },
      {
        "id":15,
        "question":"What is the full form of RAM?",
        "option1":"Read Access Memory",
        "option2":"Random Access Memory",
        "option3":"Random Accent Memory",
        "answer":"Random Access Memory"
      },
      {
        "id":16,
        "question":"How many bits is a byte?",
        "option1":"8",
        "option2":"16",
        "option3":"32",
        "answer":"8"
      },
      {
        "id":17,
        "question":"Computers calculate numbers in what mode?",
        "option1":"Octal",
        "option2":"Binary",
        "option3":"Decimal",
        "answer":"Binary"
      },
      {
        "id":18,
        "question":"The speed of your net access is defined in terms of?",
        "option1":"Kbps",
        "option2":"Megabytes",
        "option3":"MHz",
        "answer":"Kbps"
      },
      {
        "id":19,
        "question":"Which was an early mainframe computer?",
        "option1":"BRAINIA",
        "option2":"ENIAC",
        "option3":"UNIC",
        "answer":"ENIAC"
      },
      {
        "id":20,
        "question":"Which of these is not a computer?",
        "option1":"Paseo",
        "option2":"Macintosh",
        "option3":"Acorn",
        "answer":"Paseo"
      },
      {
        "id":21,
        "question":"Which of the following is not a programming language?",
        "option1":"Basic",
        "option2":"Java",
        "option3":"Turing",
        "answer":"Turing"
      },
      {
        "id":22,
        "question":"Which of the following is not a method of accessing the web?",
        "option1":"ISDN",
        "option2":"CPU",
        "option3":"DSL",
        "answer":"CPU"
      },
      {
        "id":23,
        "question":"In which decade was the Internet first implemented?",
        "option1":"1960s",
        "option2":"1970s",
        "option3":"1980s",
        "answer":"1960s"
      },
      {
        "id":24,
        "question":"Main circuit board in a computer is?",
        "option1":"Decoder",
        "option2":"Highlight",
        "option3":"Mother board",
        "answer":"Mother board"
      },
      {
        "id":25,
        "question":"Which of the following operating systems is produced by IBM?",
        "option1":"UNIX",
        "option2":"OS-2",
        "option3":"Windows",
        "answer":"OS-2"
      }
      ]
  }
}
